{"cards":[{"mId":"cddeb439-fc3d-446f-afac-374423c0205c","mCardType":"text","mFront":"(adv.) alongside each other, moving in one direction; (adj.) well informed, up to date on a subject","mBack":"abreast"},{"mId":"cd0ae1c0-1bd3-4624-a6d8-36fe075fda4e","mCardType":"text","mFront":"a standard used to evaluate similar things","mBack":"benchmark"},{"mId":"bbbb170f-3eed-448f-9025-076d6b45a5e2","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to benefit from or take advantage of something","mBack":"capitalize"},{"mId":"fc7066ab-34e7-4093-8e1a-5842f1fa6cfa","mCardType":"text","mFront":"warning against certain acts","mBack":"caveat"},{"mId":"a20dc0b6-7da0-4813-b7d1-fb9bb6694839","mCardType":"text","mFront":"an order","mBack":"command"},{"mId":"87ebb273-00b9-4c1d-a030-84d201730c04","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to separate or organize into categories or compartments","mBack":"compartmentalize"},{"mId":"ea42546f-9a51-4ec4-a255-b6f2ae3f2eb5","mCardType":"text","mFront":"a set of facts and circumstances pertaining to a situation or event","mBack":"context"},{"mId":"ff38115a-7df2-4e96-9d29-a89b0832ba3f","mCardType":"text","mFront":"an essential point requiring resolution (in an argument)","mBack":"crux"},{"mId":"c0671f31-6d4c-4bee-828e-d2b5a07b6bd4","mCardType":"text","mFront":"a statistic, like sex, age, or income, that characterizes human populations","mBack":"demographic"},{"mId":"01763ad5-1076-463d-b563-8daa92178bb0","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to give orders or demands with authority","mBack":"dictate"},{"mId":"c3690674-e9ec-4db1-a579-7d1ad2ffdf95","mCardType":"text","mFront":"the act of spending money","mBack":"expenditure"},{"mId":"9bb1e027-1a04-4599-8cd5-9dbcd58916ba","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to cause positive admiration or respect","mBack":"impress"},{"mId":"cb90e980-b572-4424-8aee-475df1c87b43","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to experience something unpleasant","mBack":"incur"},{"mId":"b36308bb-8258-4323-80d1-d302eeaf8865","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to reflect deeply on a subject","mBack":"mull"},{"mId":"4bed1ebf-1ad9-41fd-81a4-f8574a7a8fa6","mCardType":"text","mFront":"sophisticated and intuitive","mBack":"savvy"},{"mId":"c86c4705-b799-4e0a-baf2-821413c24cec","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to make more economical or efficient","mBack":"streamline"},{"mId":"770cdde5-00cb-4683-86d3-f2bea9ecf6b4","mCardType":"text","mFront":"modified by individual bias, rather than based on facts","mBack":"subjective"},{"mId":"4305f112-006f-4b0e-b38c-71139f16b48e","mCardType":"text","mFront":"done in a consistent and systematic manner","mBack":"systematically"},{"mId":"633033fc-5f48-4747-853d-a8e72b253d97","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to respect","mBack":"esteem"},{"mId":"5abd03f7-a3b5-4217-9762-35f7db160cda","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to demand and obtain something often through force or threats","mBack":"exact"},{"mId":"1b71c3b1-8212-4339-8eb3-f96fddaeaae0","mCardType":"text","mFront":"personality or temperament, including a person\u0027s typical mood and attitude","mBack":"disposition"},{"mId":"8c4077e1-c34e-456b-8b19-f595b8049bad","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to lose effectiveness, confidence, or ability","mBack":"falter"},{"mId":"545e3690-c6e8-4e51-9808-3d2bf3dd6ead","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to control and direct something for a purpose","mBack":"harness"},{"mId":"dbf84dfd-909a-4fda-a941-4c7e460b80a8","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to cause or produce","mBack":"induce"},{"mId":"001ebdf5-97f7-4364-8dae-5596ccde8f36","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to give out in small portions","mBack":"allot"},{"mId":"3a1003d4-d1ef-4efb-ae52-a341fa6726e7","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to accomplish something by being clever and creative","mBack":"contrive"},{"mId":"a779e9b1-2c97-4662-b0b7-544b3d2527ea","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to create, invent or creatively think up an idea or plan","mBack":"devise"},{"mId":"55315a6b-30cf-4213-b030-c00b900de0b9","mCardType":"text","mFront":"the most important, before all else","mBack":"foremost"},{"mId":"4614bd9f-d709-49dd-9ed4-586bf75ffd73","mCardType":"text","mFront":"something that encourages action","mBack":"incentive"},{"mId":"6fe0acc5-1ed1-4ff8-a449-99e336b2d3ea","mCardType":"text","mFront":"new and original","mBack":"novel"},{"mId":"467bff1e-85e7-4912-95a5-5fc9a7b18d68","mCardType":"text","mFront":"burden, duty, or responsibility","mBack":"onus"},{"mId":"633badb9-e2eb-478b-802d-b52f6fa58c17","mCardType":"text","mFront":"suitable for a purpose or occurring at the right time","mBack":"opportune"},{"mId":"45a78631-62a6-449d-93b7-0aeff5053da4","mCardType":"text","mFront":"open to view, not hidden","mBack":"overt"},{"mId":"eff3cb8b-b185-4053-b4df-b457b4fd02b0","mCardType":"text","mFront":"an introduction at the beginning of a book","mBack":"preface"},{"mId":"c5011f0f-a2ae-4e11-86af-a53256665664","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to send or dispatch a payment","mBack":"remit"},{"mId":"bdeb5216-1156-4924-b01e-e14eda90b161","mCardType":"text","mFront":"spoken shortly and often rudely--terse","mBack":"curt"},{"mId":"08782d09-8044-4106-b7f3-a450f691410c","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to make similar, esp. by absorption into a culture or population","mBack":"assimilate"},{"mId":"5a375a26-3055-4d9b-835e-b03da97856c2","mCardType":"text","mFront":"a person\u0027s outward behavior, manner, or appearance, especially as it reflects on mood or character","mBack":"demeanor"},{"mId":"f611956e-6c2c-45cf-8c28-853a15d88d4e","mCardType":"text","mFront":"extremely and blatantly bad","mBack":"egregious"},{"mId":"669e078e-a5f6-4319-afbb-50698188aa21","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to banish or exile someone from a country","mBack":"expatriate"},{"mId":"6a5371b3-0a56-457e-84fb-32ae4ec05413","mCardType":"text","mFront":"an aspect of something","mBack":"facet"},{"mId":"1046f16f-7a76-46bf-ab62-d90156a68151","mCardType":"text","mFront":"in the beginning of development or formation","mBack":"incipient"},{"mId":"786ac51b-1375-431a-872b-f901b3aed8e3","mCardType":"text","mFront":"wishing to hurt others","mBack":"malicious"},{"mId":"79f1135e-84f9-4662-89e0-95415dc5c65a","mCardType":"text","mFront":"evil, life-threatening","mBack":"malignant"},{"mId":"3d8bd66a-038f-4d65-9e15-b5df69edb894","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to give birth or to cause something new to grow","mBack":"spawn"},{"mId":"d59091aa-1fbd-4d5a-9e32-ecf405abba11","mCardType":"text","mFront":"highly involved or complex, made up of many different parts","mBack":"intricate"},{"mId":"b39299ac-187c-446f-9b7a-531f80ab5918","mCardType":"text","mFront":"something horrible or shameful","mBack":"abomination"},{"mId":"f3aca9b6-48b0-4e9d-ad8b-d38b190a149d","mCardType":"text","mFront":"an extreme description or exaggeration of someone or something done for comic effect","mBack":"caricature"},{"mId":"0a8036f7-29ed-41b0-8321-581f13e6458f","mCardType":"text","mFront":"having to do with citizens or the general population","mBack":"civil"},{"mId":"0054eede-9cd4-42c1-a0ff-f784b62fdb05","mCardType":"text","mFront":"trite expression or phrase","mBack":"cliche"},{"mId":"5ec4c186-1152-4141-a87e-9896558ec3c8","mCardType":"text","mFront":"a musical performance","mBack":"concert"},{"mId":"42b3d745-22cd-42b8-b018-ec98ff69051b","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to criticize as wrong or immoral","mBack":"condemn"},{"mId":"aceef962-54b1-4e3c-b8f8-73980093db5a","mCardType":"text","mFront":"tending to promote or encourage something to happen or exist--having the right conditions for something","mBack":"conducive"},{"mId":"8e8738be-5396-47ec-ac2a-610d307240f0","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to follow a rule or instructions","mBack":"adhere"},{"mId":"d622e825-032b-4e10-a2b6-7d5d0a66c250","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to enhance or make more attractive with decoration or ornament","mBack":"adorn"},{"mId":"284d76c4-76e2-4eaa-8d38-159e282fe7a5","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to treat or regard somebody with admiration and deep respect","mBack":"revere"},{"mId":"bcd6edb1-c487-4068-b1e2-cbd9769386fa","mCardType":"text","mFront":"a lavish or extravagant amount","mBack":"profusion"},{"mId":"85121ed9-ad48-4cdd-8fa0-431af651269d","mCardType":"text","mFront":"completely free of interruption and disturbance--calm","mBack":"placid"},{"mId":"4d25ee31-46a2-43b9-b40e-33b10a570f83","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to relieve or lessen","mBack":"alleviate"},{"mId":"f006e100-1817-419f-bb12-0925526d9466","mCardType":"text","mFront":"unnecessary fuss or excited activity over something","mBack":"ado"},{"mId":"1ba212c0-7aa0-4487-b657-fc2f98a444a6","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to be plentiful","mBack":"abound"},{"mId":"470b288c-e254-4be9-88ce-33924c1e50d4","mCardType":"text","mFront":"help or advantage in something","mBack":"avail"},{"mId":"b5114887-3cc4-455d-93e3-2756b58a01bb","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to describe the character or characteristics of somebody or something","mBack":"characterize"},{"mId":"82020105-07ab-4cc4-96e8-77bd0bd9dcd8","mCardType":"text","mFront":"sticking, holding, or working together as a unit","mBack":"cohesive"},{"mId":"78421a46-0228-450c-bea7-94b9e17dcdaa","mCardType":"text","mFront":"the quality of being consistent and uninterrupted throughout","mBack":"continuity"},{"mId":"8156f146-6ea2-4ee3-abf1-d98d631eb886","mCardType":"text","mFront":"having experience, familiarity, or knowledge (usually followed by \"with\" or \"in\")","mBack":"conversant"},{"mId":"ab96e983-35a8-4f6b-ae68-d7f0314154ba","mCardType":"text","mFront":"the number below the line in a fraction","mBack":"denominator"},{"mId":"82ebf84e-b246-4a17-8443-ebc4838715d9","mCardType":"text","mFront":"highly serious and sincere in manner or attitude","mBack":"earnest"},{"mId":"e43300dd-2185-4fed-a587-eddf0bba6637","mCardType":"text","mFront":"an element contributing to the result of something","mBack":"factor"},{"mId":"5eee247e-933e-4018-bb0d-2c7f474777fe","mCardType":"text","mFront":"expressing true opinion","mBack":"frank"},{"mId":"fb9271a3-1eee-4918-87ef-02ab2abcecc7","mCardType":"text","mFront":"a sudden or ongoing arrival of many things or of a lot of people","mBack":"influx"},{"mId":"9d081b93-3b5d-48be-b330-e83ea4cc7a23","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to protect something or prevent the transfer to heat, cold, or sound by surrounding it in insulating materials","mBack":"insulate"},{"mId":"ef0d5f5d-f0a1-4ec7-9807-79918a26c6f7","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to say or insert something in a way that interrupts what is being said or discussed","mBack":"interject"},{"mId":"060418cb-5acc-47b9-b27f-eeb2553c3fa9","mCardType":"text","mFront":"foremost in importance or power","mBack":"paramount"},{"mId":"4b8b8809-ed0c-4484-abd0-c8a1eeb1aaf0","mCardType":"text","mFront":"point of view","mBack":"perspective"},{"mId":"43c9ff90-724a-4ffe-bedb-d1c75231246d","mCardType":"text","mFront":"the possibility of future success","mBack":"prospect"},{"mId":"7fea0409-6328-40ea-8f37-d242b5f6d5e6","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to return to an earlier, worse condition","mBack":"regress"},{"mId":"a589d094-aac0-4f00-ac77-71732badb787","mCardType":"text","mFront":"healthy, strong, and energetic","mBack":"robust"},{"mId":"f555de8f-1af8-4b44-8c92-e66fe913d23b","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to make someone experience something unpleasant","mBack":"subject"},{"mId":"b52b8637-69d3-46e5-8674-d4dd15011848","mCardType":"text","mFront":"the time spent in a particular office or position","mBack":"tenure"},{"mId":"bfaeaad9-3313-44d1-b27a-9719586606e7","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to rise above or go beyond the limits of something","mBack":"transcend"},{"mId":"aa674f7e-af01-4257-ac90-cbb5a4595141","mCardType":"text","mFront":"agreement as to the right course of action","mBack":"accordance"},{"mId":"0d3b23c2-5afe-462e-b9eb-ca3cf974a43c","mCardType":"text","mFront":"insincere or feigned behavior meant to deceive","mBack":"pretense"},{"mId":"6f6d0b68-ab41-4f5b-8d4a-452c3de333d7","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to obtain something by special effort","mBack":"procure"},{"mId":"1d442adc-f5c1-43e2-b180-e3d53b28806b","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to lessen the intensity of something","mBack":"allay"},{"mId":"41b2bd82-f046-4369-8fe0-03f41fdb9094","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to explain according to or to give credit to","mBack":"attribute"},{"mId":"af052216-d5f5-4ea1-adc6-001fcc2dfc5e","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to go around something in order to avoid it","mBack":"circumvent"},{"mId":"f17d50bc-2667-47b1-baef-ab5c66f8fe54","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to create something imaginative by combining ingredients in a new, unplanned way, especially in cooking","mBack":"concoct"},{"mId":"a349a19f-fb8e-4e36-b954-4dd07797cc05","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to interpret or assign meaning to","mBack":"construe"},{"mId":"8d7c5211-7f3c-4bc0-961e-e791ba31cd7c","mCardType":"text","mFront":"the quality of being near or close together","mBack":"proximity"},{"mId":"f79e4ae7-e900-4c75-a5aa-9c2c281c41df","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to reproduce or create a model of something","mBack":"simulate"},{"mId":"815da118-3cd2-402e-b189-f56c78546c54","mCardType":"text","mFront":"equivalent to a particular thing in effect, outcome, or value--the same as","mBack":"tantamount"},{"mId":"0089b3b9-9d38-493e-95e7-4abb5110c0ed","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to rebuke or scold somebody mildly, but earnestly","mBack":"admonish"},{"mId":"69e1f9f2-6bf7-4ba9-a11f-5ac95f7750dd","mCardType":"text","mFront":"something formed by adding together several amounts or things","mBack":"aggregate"},{"mId":"d5173fb9-9def-4131-a897-19608511ba6a","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to strongly urge someone to do something","mBack":"exhort"},{"mId":"999043f8-b086-47e0-8f98-312b6c7b1117","mCardType":"text","mFront":"a security pledged for the repayment of a loan","mBack":"collateral"},{"mId":"151b0e9b-14d6-474d-8fe5-0601f01f2839","mCardType":"text","mFront":"a standard used to judge things","mBack":"criterion"},{"mId":"8ec2df4b-cd96-4d69-b9c4-5f218e6684cd","mCardType":"text","mFront":"protected from being removed or taken away","mBack":"inalienable"},{"mId":"ec7706d2-d643-4b75-9a9f-30dddc0c1aa7","mCardType":"text","mFront":"a subtle difference, distinction or variation in something","mBack":"nuance"},{"mId":"31ea88a8-f6c5-4409-a13a-56afd45aba4b","mCardType":"text","mFront":"a final judgment of guilty in a criminal case and the punishment that is imposed","mBack":"conviction"}]}